Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v):
[!] Flutter (Channel stable, 3.41.4, on Microsoft Windows [Version 10.0.26200.8037], locale en-IN)
    ! The flutter binary is not on your path. Consider adding C:\flutter\bin to your path.
    ! The dart binary is not on your path. Consider adding C:\flutter\bin to your path.
[ΓêÜ] Windows Version (11 Home Single Language 64-bit, 25H2, 2009)
[!] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices (Android SDK version 36.1.0)
    X cmdline-tools component is missing.
      Try installing or updating Android Studio.
      Alternatively, download the tools from https://developer.android.com/studio#command-line-tools-only and make sure to set the ANDROID_HOME environment variable.
      See https://developer.android.com/studio/command-line for more details.
    X Android license status unknown.
      Run `flutter doctor --android-licenses` to accept the SDK licenses.
      See https://flutter.dev/to/windows-android-setup for more details.
[ΓêÜ] Chrome - develop for the web
[X] Visual Studio - develop Windows apps
    X Visual Studio not installed; this is necessary to develop Windows apps.
      Download at https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/.
      Please install the "Desktop development with C++" workload, including all of its default components
[ΓêÜ] Connected device (3 available)
[ΓêÜ] Network resources

! Doctor found issues in 3 categories.
